{
    "multiplication": [
        {
            "question":"5 * 1",
            "answer":"5"
        },
        {
            "question":"6 * 2",
            "answer":"12"
        },
        {
            "question":"10 * 10",
            "answer":"100"
        },
        {
            "question":"5 * 5",
            "answer":"25"
        },
        {
            "question":"3 * 3",
            "answer":"9"
        },
        {
            "question":"8 * 2",
            "answer":"16"
        },
        {
            "question":"23 * 2",
            "answer":"46"
        },
        {
            "question":"12 * 3",
            "answer":"36"
        },
        {
            "question":"5 * 4",
            "answer":"20"
        },
        {
            "question":"7 * 7",
            "answer":"49"
        },
        {
            "question":"4 * 4",
            "answer":"16"
        }
        
    ]
}